

PROFILE

I have good experience on WordPress Theme development and Plugin. I am working in WordPress more than 6 years and already developed a lot of website and theme for my customers. I have a large knowledge of responsive design too.

I also have good knowledge of PrestaShop, Shopify, Magento, Cpanel, FTP, Server, Debugging etc.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+8801556434001

WEBSITE:

https://duetsoft.com https://xltheme.com

FM All

ikrama.213@gmail.com

SOCIAL:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ikrama https://www.facebook.com/kh.ikrama

HOBBIES

Reading Travelling

KHANDAKER IKRAMA

WordPress Developer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Duetsoft, Sr. Web Developer May 2016–Present

XLTHEME, WordPress Developer August 2015–Present

ThemeXpert, Joomla Developer

March 2016-May 2018

Joomla Template development, Improvement of Quix Joomla page builder and providing tech support for the customer.

ThemePicasso, Front end Developer

April 2015-May 2016

UpWork, WordPress and Front-end Developer

September 2010-March 2016

EDUCATION

MSc, Dhaka University Going

BSc Hons, National University

CGPA 2.74 out of 4

SKILLS

WordPress

HTML

CSS

LESS

PHP

JavaScript

Git

Server

Debugging etc.